[Ready or not,]
[here I come.]
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]
[Anyone who wants to play hide-and-seek, gather around here.]
[The sunsets beyond the mountains.]
[Finally arrived at a remote retreat center]
[after hours of driving in the dark.]
[An unexplainable, eerie energy fills this place.]
SHOTARO!
Hey, SOHEE!
Hey guys! Where are you?!
[The 6 members of RIIZE are left in this place.]
Where are you, RIIZE?
I'm just going to hide.
I can’t do this. I’m too scared.
Wait. Hold on. Where am I?
Pause. Pause.
This is really scary.
Ha...
What the…
I guess it's starting now.
Woah, hold on.
I have a bad feeling about this.
[The moment of confronting an unknown being.]
[You can never escape.]
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]
Oh, no.
I’m screwed.
Woah, hold on.
Where is this place?
What is this?
[Each member of RIIZE opens their eyes in a different place.]
Where am I?
[What they see before them is completely different.]
Ah...
Why am I in here?
What the...?
What is this place?
Hold on. Did the game start?
Can I move around?
Hold on. Wait a minute.
What should I do?
[SUNGCHAN is located on B1.]
[ANTON is located on 1F.]
[SHOTARO is located on 2F.]
[SOHEE and EUNSEOK are located on the 3rd floor.]
[WONBIN is located on the 4th floor.]
[Phone alarm goes off]
Wait, hold on.
Be quiet, be quiet, be quiet, be quiet.
[From this moment on,
find the keys that only the brave can obtain]
[If you are captured by the seeker,
you can use the keys to escape.
(However, one key per person to escape.)]
SAVE ME
Keys?
Find the keys?
[The members started to move after checking the message.]
[SOHEE is located on the 3rd floor.]
[Sound of the phone dropping.]
[EUNSEOK and SOHEE are located on the 3rd floor.]
[EUNSEOK sighing]
Hide-and-seek really is...
scary just thinking that
someone is out there trying to catch me.
This is the food storage room.
[SUNGCHAN is located on the 1st floor.]
Where should I hide?
My main goal is
hiding. Hiding from the seeker.
Why is this scary for no good reason?
Should I hide here?
I think this is a good spot.
This spot
has a lot of desks and chairs
and I’m sitting on the corner of it.
This is terrifying.
[SUNGCHAN →]
There is…
no point of finding the keys
because
I just don’t need to get caught.
The keys...
are not my business, sorry.
[SUNGCHAN laughing]
[ANTON is located on the 1st floor.]
[At the same time on the 1st floor.]
Because I am a coward…
Do I have to start hiding?
[ANTON has similar thoughts to SUNGCHAN]
I’m just going to hide.
I can’t do it.
It’s too scary.
Oh no...
[ANTON →]
(Hiding) This may be my best choice…
This may be my best at trying.
I’ll try to stay put here.
If not, then, I hope someone comes to tell me?
But really, if the seeker comes and finds me here,
I think I'll be really scared.
Can I move this?
I mean…
I can't move right now, right?
Can I come out now?
[Scanning the surroundings.]
[Slowly makes his way out of the elevator.]
Can I come out and move around?
Do I have to hide right away?
[WONBIN sighing]
I'm not really good at these.
[While most of the members are confused.]
[EUNSEOK is located on the 3rd floor.]
[EUNSEOK is looking for the keys.]
There’s nothing here.
Forget about the hiding,
I have no clue where the keys are.
There’s absolutely nothing here.
Ha… This is really.
Ha... This is quite frustrating.
The thought of someone trying to catch me
makes me really careful whenever I move.
I get sensitive to every sound
and even now I can hear footsteps
and doors opening…
I’m getting confused if it’s my members making the sound or if it’s the seeker,
so I have to be careful when I move.
[SOHEE is located on the 4th floor.]
[On the other hand, SOHEE is confidently(?) moving around.]
Can I enter these places too?
The keys aren't in here.
(Right now) Time to look for the keys.
[Sound of the door opening and closing.]
Ahh, hold on.
[A blanket spread out on the floor of the room.]
(Doubting his eyes.)
Ahh, hold on.
[There’s someone underneath the blanket?]
Don’t prank me like this!
[SOHEE lifts up the blanket.]
Yikes!
Wow.
[Finds the key placed next to the hand.]
Look! It’s the key! key! key! key!
I found a key.
[Starts looking for another key right after.]
Oh? Hey!
Hey!
[ SOHEE runs into WONBIN
who was coming down the stairs.]
Where were you?
In the elevator.
I was stuck in the elevator!
Hey, you wanna stay together?
No,no
Just this once.
No,no,no,no
Just this time!
Let’s go together, just this once.
No, we’re screwed if we get caught by the seeker.
Please, just this once...
The sound of that smoke makes it more scary.
Right?
[Smoke sound effect]
[Both get scared by the loud sound.]
Is it the smoke sound?
[Eventually, they move to the 2nd floor together.]
[SHOTARO is in the 2nd floor storage room.]
I can’t call the members with this, right?
I don’t have their
contacts.
Should I go look for the key?
But where is it?
What is this?
I don’t know for sure what this is
but there’s a box.
[Opening the box.]
What’s this?
What is this?
Isn't it a letter? A letter.
[An unidentifiable white sheet of paper →]
[Sound of someone outside the door.]
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I heard a noise!
I have to stay quiet.
[Hurries and hides himself in the corner of the room.]
[At that moment, the door opens.]
I think it’s gonna be in here (the key).
[SOHEE and WONBIN enter the storage room.]
Hey!
AH! You scared me!
What is it?! What is it!? What is it!?
You scared me!
[← SHOTARO]
[An unexpected get-together.]
You scared me! I thought you were the seeker.
Hey, I missed you!
Where were you hiding?
But, where did you meet SOHEE ?
The stairs!
Ah-ha, the stairs.
[SOHEE heading to the stairs again.]
Should we open the elevator?
I opened the elevator door and the key was right there.
Ah, really?
[A mysterious object encountered right after opening the eyes.]
This is really scary.
[Carefully lifting up the black cloth.]
Uh, what is this?
[Obtained the key beneath the black cloth.]
[WONBIN and SHOTARO are located on the 2nd floor.]
I’m extremely happy seeing you.
But you’re not the seeker, right?
No, I’m not.
I think the keys are hiding somewhere here.
Wait...
There’s nowhere to hide here.
I hope they don’t ask us to dance to ‘Siren’ as part of a mission later.
Ah… should I just get caught by the seeker?
No!
How about here?
Can we go in?
[Sound of someone coming from far away.]
[WONBIN hiding in one corner.]
[SHOTARO hiding on the stairs.]
[Checking to see where the sound came from.]
[← Someone approaching from far ahead.]
Who is it?
It’s me, WONBIN.
[The source of the sound was SOHEE.]
I think
right now isn’t the time to hide.
Really?
We are supposed to look for the keys right now.
Ah, we have to look for the keys?
Oh, then I’m going to walk freely as well.
I was scared for nothing.
Can we open anywhere we like?
[SHOTARO is located on the 1st floor. ]
[Unexpectedly, SHOTARO got separated from WONBIN.]
[Enters a random room on the 1st floor.]
WONBIN...
Where did WONBIN go?
Uh... I guess someone was here?
There’s a sleep mask.
[Actually, this place is where ANTON is hiding.]
[ANTON →]
[Without knowing the truth,
SHOTARO eagerly searches for the keys.]
What is that?
[SHOTARO and ANTON laughing.]
Did you hear me coming?
Just now.
I was here the whole time.
You scared me!
SHOTARO,
can you cover the top with this?
What?
You want me to cover you up?
Yea...
When did you come?
I was here this whole time from the beginning.
Why here? You scared me!
I had no clue someone was going to be in here...
[Phone alarm goes off.]
[Hint for the key.]
[Food storage room on B1.]
It’s in the basement.
This is the 1st floor, right?
But...
if you have the courage, then you should go.
If you don't, then just stay here
like me.
SHOTARO!
Before you leave, can you cover this up?
Ah, what are you doing?!
Cover it up properly!
Is this an easy hiding spot?
No.
[SHOTARO hides ANTON.]
[Makes his way to find the key.]
Bye, I’m going!
Don’t leave me!
[Opens the door and leaves ANTON by himself.]
Auditorium.
There’s nothing here.
[Familiar voice coming nearer.]
[SHOTARO →]
[WONBIN and SOHEE on the 1st floor.]
ANTON is in here.
ANTON! ANTON! ANTON!
ANTON!
[ANTON ↓]
ANTON is in here. Did you see him?
We need to find the key.
[Heading to the basement where the key is located.]
Is everyone here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don’t leave me.
Who is it?
[ANTON by himself again.]
Should I come out?
[ANTON’s deep sigh.]
No,
staying here
is safer than coming out.
[Decides to stay and hides himself again. ]
[Another person hiding as well.]
[Phone alarm goes off.]
[SUNGCHAN checks the hint for finding the key.]
The food storage room...
I think it was
the first room I went in.
Should I go look for the key now?
[Mysterious loud sound.]
But just now
I heard a noise somewhere here
so I’ll leave
after 5 minutes.
[ SHOTARO, WONBIN and SOHEE are heading over to the basement.]
This is the cafeteria.
The members are here!
I was…
I was the only one hiding?
[Sound of the kitchen curtain open.]
That’s the food storage room!
Isn’t it?
[← SUNGCHAN coming out from hiding.]
Isn’t this the place?
What was that?
Who is that?
Who’s there?!
- It’s SUNGCHAN?
- SUNGCHAN.
[Laugh of relief.]
[SUNGCHAN joins the members.]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I know where the food storage room is.
It’s here.
It’s not here.
Come here!
It wasn’t on the first floor?
This is the food storage room.
[Everyone heading over to the food storage room.]
I was first born(?) here.
Really?
Were you here this whole time?
Yea, I was here the whole time.
[Leaving without finding the key.]
[SUNGCHAN coming back.]
I have a feeling there’s something in here.
What is this?
It looks like a trap
There’s a trap.
There’s a trap in here.
There’s a key in here but it looks like a trap.
Can I put my hand inside?
Put it in.
[← The key inside the trap.]
Can I put my hand in?
It’s the key!
[Obtained the key in the food storage room.]
So, this is the food storage room?
Oh, so the key is
located in the spot
[Phone alarm goes off.]
you were first in.
[Second hint for the key arrived.]
We got a message.
[Hint for the key.]
[Flower bed on the 1st floor.]
[Mysterious scream.]
[The source of the eerie screams was EUNSEOK,
who came down a few moments later.]
I came down to look for the key.
[SOHEE, WONBIN and SUNGCHAN each obtained one key. ]
Is there even a seeker?
I don’t think there’s a seeker as of now.
I think they want us to find the keys.
Maybe the game will start after finding all the keys?
So, we should hurry up and find the keys.
Did you find the key?
We found it!
You found the key?
We did! It was in the food storage room!
How many did we find?
[As of now, three keys are found.]
I think the seeker will start to move once we find all the keys.
So, six (keys) in total?
Ah, there’s no seeker right now?
I don’t think so.
Because we need the keys in order to save people.
I think the game will start after finding all the keys.
[Let’s go look for the keys first.]
[Phone alarm goes off.]
Hint for the key… Flower bed on the 1st floor.
Keep up the good work, everyone!
[SOHEE heads off to the 1st floor.]
So, the game officially starts after finding all the keys.
Where is the flower bed?
[One by one, the members gather on the 1st floor.]
I can’t see anything.
I really can’t see anything.
There’s too much smoke?
I’m going to hide now.
What?
The 1st floor flower bed is over here.
The members are here to look for it.
They’re over there.
Did you find the key?
I'm not sure.
I can’t see anything.
Is this the 1st floor?
This is the 1st floor flower bed.
[WONBIN stepping on top of the flower bed.]
I found it. I found it.
You found it?
[The key is hanging on the tree branch.]
[As he is lifting the key.]
Woah.
(Assessing the situation.)
[You found it?]
[Now, I’m the seeker.]
[Ready or not,]
[here I come.]
[SUNCHAN is located on the 1st floor.]
[SUNGCHAN and SHOTARO are located on the 1st floor.]
[SHOTARO and SUNGCHAN ran away to the 1st floor bathroom.]
[EUNSEOK is already on the 4th floor.]
[SOHEE is located on the 2nd floor.]
[SOHEE hides himself in the 2nd floor storage room.]
[WONBIN is located on the 3rd floor.]
[WONBIN heads over to the 3rd floor]
[Let’s begin the game of hide-and-seek.]
Wow, why is this so scary?
[WONBIN is located on the 3rd floor.]
This is so unfair.
[Phone alarm goes off.]
[We will begin the hide-and-seek now.]
[The playtime is 4,444 seconds.]
[If you get caught by the seeker, you’ll be locked up somewhere.]
(Hide-and-seek) The game will begin now.
[Hide-and-seek is a game where your survival rate is very important.
If your survival rate is over 50%]
[BRIIZE will receive a great gift]
[so please try your best at hiding yourself.]
It was starting now.
I’m screwed, screwed, screwed.
[Ready or not,]
[here I come.]
I think the seeker started to make its move.
This is seriously not right.
[Ready or not,]
[here I come.]
Earlier
when the seeker woke up
its (seeker) visual was insanely scary.
The 'Hide-and-seek' song is really scary.
[SUNGCHAN, SHOTARO, the seeker and ANTON are located on the 1st floor.]
[Three people are hiding on the 1st floor.]
SUNGCHAN, I’m coming out now.
[Sound of the door opening.]
[The seeker and SHOTARO are located on the 1st floor.]
Uh-oh… I hear the seeker.
[← SHOTARO] [The seeker →]
[SHOTARO changed his direction after noticing the seeker.]
[Safely arrives at the auditorium on the 1st floor.]
Woah, that scared me.
[Decides to hide behind the curtains.]
[SOHEE heads over to the 3rd floor.]
[Sound of someone nearby.]
You scared me.
Who is that?
Hide, hide!
[Decides to move instead of hiding.]
[ANTON →]
[The sound of the seeker’s cane.]
Ah…what is that sound?
I just
want to be locked up already.
[The seeker is still on the 1st floor.]
[The seeker enters the room ANTON is hiding in.]
[ANTON →]
[Leaves without noticing him.]
[Sound of ANTON breathing.]
[SHOTARO, the seeker and SUNGCHAN are located on the 1st floor.]
[SHOTARO leaves the auditorium.]
[After noticing the seeker,
he returns to the auditorium.]
It was the seeker...
[The seeker enters the 1st floor hallway.]
Who’s there?
[At the end of the hallway are WONBIN and SOHEE!]
[WONBIN in the far corner at the end of the hallway.]
[The sound of the seeker’s cane.]
[WONBIN & SOHEE →]
[← SOHEE]
[ SOHEE, I found you!]
[WONBIN, who was near SOHEE.]
I wanna go home, I wanna go home, I wanna go home, please.
[← WONBIN]
[Hides in the flower bed
where the seeker woke up.]
[One of the members has been locked up
in the basement prison.]
Bye, SOHEE.
What? SOHEE is already in prison?
I’m the first one to get captured?
[If you don’t escape the prison within 20 minutes,
you are locked up until the playtime is over.]
[
With the key : Call the gatekeeper and hand over the key.
Without the key : Use the member's contact number written inside the prison and request for a rescue.]
[SHOTARO and SUNGCHAN are located on the 1st floor.]
SUNGCHAN!
Yes.
Hand me the key.
Did someone get captured?
I'm not sure.
[SUNGCHAN hands over the key to SHOTARO.]
I’ll stay here.
I’ll go rescue him.
[SOHEE already has a key.]
[SHOTARO arrives at the prison.]
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
What was the seeker like?
What did it look like?
Hurry up and run first.
[Successfully rescues SOHEE with SUNGCHAN’s key.]
Why, why, why, why?
Is the seeker here?
No, never mind.
[SOHEE and SHOTARO are located on B1.]
For now, SOHEE is safe.
Hey, SOHEE!
Who has the key?
You don’t have one?
I do!
You have one?
Yea, but you saved me.
You just need to hide.
Okay, I’ll hide now.
[SHOTARO moves to a different location.]
[WONBIN is located on the 1st floor.]
[← The tree where the key was hanging from.]
[WONBIN comes out from the flower bed.]
[Obtained the key where he had dropped it when the seeker woke up.]
[Sudden sound of the seeker’s cane.]
[Heads over to WONBIN’s direction.]
[WONBIN hiding behind the counter.]
[The distance between them is getting closer.]
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]